欢迎光临威廉斯堡餐厅
Welcome to the Williamsburg Diner.
这一顿饭将助你缩年减寿
Your lifespan just decreased by one meal.
你是要现在点餐
Would you like to order now
还是等那星系被毁灭后点
or after that galaxy is destroyed?
兄弟 我也能对你竖起一根手指
Oh, dude, I can hold up one finger, too,
相信我 绝对不是食指
and trust me; it won't be that one.
一号卡座归你了
Booth one is all yours.
如果我想跟一个
If I wanted to deal with a guy
不愿正视我存在的男人打交道
who won't even acknowledge my existence,
我早去找我爹了
I'd track down my father.
妆容得填补你个性上的不足
Makeup needs to complement the personality.
抱歉 没在听
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
眼后正要教我怎么拔眉毛
Mr. Eye Queen's about to show me how to pluck my eyebrows.
终于啊
Finally.
我都跟你说了一年了 你得拔拔眉毛
I've been telling you for a year you need to get plucked.
上菜 半熟蛋
Pick up. Fried egg over easy.
修正 是全"硬"
Correction: make that over hard.
麦克斯 那是厄尔点的
Max, that's Earl's order.
帮忙一下吧
Can you?
我也能时间一到下班走人
You know, I could just check out
工作时浑水摸鱼啊
and phone in this job, too,
但我答应过自己
but I promised myself
长大后绝不当我妇科医生那样的人
I'd never grow up to be my gynecologist.
厄尔 我知道你一定还记得
Earl, I know you remember a time
人们彼此间会有眼神交流
where people still made eye contact
能看到我眼中鄙视的那段美好时光
and get the fact that I was totally dissing them.
真是太遗憾了 麦克斯
It's a damn shame, Max.
谢谢 厄尔
Thank you, Earl.
纽约大都会棒球队六局下半了还落后
The Mets are down in the bottom of the sixth.
连你都有智能手机了吗
Now you have one?
厄尔 三个月之前
Earl, three months ago,
你还以为T电信是饶舌歌手名呢
you thought T-Mobile was a rapper.
麦克斯 我想跟你说件事
Max, I want to talk to you.
有何不可
Well, why not?
大家也都在听着亚洲产的
Everyone else is listening to something tiny
小东西说话
and made in Asia.
我刚听到了世上最好笑的笑话
I just heard the funniest joke.
有个男的开车上坡
A guy is driving a car up a hill
他看到路上有只猪
and he sees a pig in the road.
对了 我忘了一部分
Wait. Oh yes, I forgot.
当时正下着雨
It's raining.
当时正下着雨 路上有只猪
It's raining, and there is a pig.
我听着呢
I'm listening.
然后猪在车子上
And then the pig is in the car--
不对 猪在路上
no, the pig is in the road,
然后... 我马上回来
and--I'll be right back.
谢谢 欢迎再度光临
Thank you. Come again.
今晚下班后你想做什么
Hey, what do you want to do after work tonight?
我们可以一起去那家很潮只卖果汁的
Maybe we could go to that trendy new ice cream place
新冰激凌店啊
that only sells juice.
不要 我太累了
Nah, I'm too tired.
我从03年开始就没坐下休息过
I've been on my feet since 2003.
我能要一个红丝绒...
Hi, can I get a red velvet--
天啊 麦克斯·布莱克[黑]
Oh, my God, Max Black?
我勒个去 贝姬·怀特[白]
Oh, my God, Becky White?
哇靠 我们都多久没见面了
Holy crap. How long has it been?
我上次上《批斗会》节目是哪年的事了
Let's see. When was I on "Intervention"?
你的头发又长回好看的那边了
Well, your hair's grown back on the right side,
所以我猜大概五年了吧
so I'd say five years.
你好 我叫卡洛琳
Hi, I'm Caroline.
我也想等麦克斯跟你介绍我
I'd wait for Max to introduce me,
但她通常告诉别人
but she usually tells people
我是泰勒·斯威夫特弱智的表姐 兰蒂
I'm Taylor Swift's slow cousin Randi.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
麦克斯 我真没想到你还活着
Max, I did not think you would still be alive.
那我赌输你十块
I owe you $10.
贝姬是个女演员
Becky's an actress.
我才看了她出演电视剧《法律与秩序》
I just saw her in "Law and Order."
她演"跟被害人不太熟的熟食店员"超精彩
She owned "Deli worker who barely knew the victim."
对啊 我演过三次《法律与秩序》了
Yeah, I've done three "Law and Orders."
工作挺简单的
Pretty easy work.
我的尸首通常在某人后车厢被人发现
They usually find me in a trunk.
你们怎么认识的
How do you two know each other?
麦克斯跟我以前一起当过服务员
Max and I waited tables together.
其实通常就干站着跟喝醉酒
Well, mostly stood around and got drunk,
但还是薪水拿啊
but they paid us.
小店不错
Nice shop.
看来你们俩也一起做生意啊
Looks like you guys have a business together too.
也有
Too?
你们也有过吗
You two too?
我们发明了只服务女性的优步
We invented an Uber just for women.
奶步
Boober.
其实应该挺有前景的
It would've been awesome,
不过我们没有软件 或车
except we didn't have an app...or a car.
别管这小蛋糕店了
Hey, forget about this cupcake.
我刚发薪水
I just got paid.
我请喝酒怎么样
How about drinks on me?
我说的请喝酒 是指一人一瓶蓝带啤酒
And by drinks, I mean one PBR each.
我也不介意喝一杯
I guess I could do drinks.
能麻烦你负责打烊吗 谢啦
Do you mind closing up? Thanks.
我出来前门找你
I'll meet you out front.
赞
Awesome.
很高兴认识你 布兰蒂
Nice meeting you, Brandi.
是兰蒂
It's Randi!
厄尔 还好吗[摇晃]
Hey, Earl, what's shaking?
麦克斯 我都要80岁了
Max, I'm pushing 80.
你问"有啥不在摇晃"比较好答
The easier question is, "What isn't shaking?"
麦克斯 你昨晚上哪去了
Max, where were you last night?
害我得自己看《卡森·达利秀》
I had to watch "Carson Daly" alone and say,
然后跟自己吐槽"这节目还在播啊"
"This show's still on?" to no one.
我昨晚在贝姬家沙发上睡了
I crashed on Becky's couch,
而且 说了你也不敢信
of which-- you're not gonna believe this--
沙发居然是她新买的呢
she is the first owner.
你们昨晚玩得开心吗
So did you guys have fun last night,
还是已渐行渐远所以挺尴尬
or was it weird because you've grown apart?
这么说吧 我俩好到要去参加
Let's just say we're gonna be in not one,
两个婚礼了
but two wedding albums.
贝姬可会跳犹太婚礼圆圈舞呢
Becky can dance her some hora.
好玩
Fun.
你玩得好真是太好玩了
That's so fun that you had fun.
你这是闹哪样
Uh, what's happening here?
我以为我们是...
I guess I just thought we were...
算了 不说了
Forget it.
千万别
Oh, no, please.
这就像在看一只鸟要撞上窗户的慢动作版
It's like watching a bird fly into a window in slow motion.
我还以为我们专属彼此
Well, you know, I thought we were exclusive,
我想不到更好的词了
for lack of a better word.
"一夫一妻"这样的词吗
What, like monogamous?
你觉得我们是一夫一妻般的友谊吗
You thought we were in a monogamous friendship?
我跟我该一夫一妻的人 都不是一夫一妻制了
I'm not even monogamous with the people I'm monogamous with.
这有啥大不了啊
What is the big deal?
在我们成为朋友前 你也有朋友啊
You had friends before we were friends.
一帮有钱婊
Bunch of rich bitches.
你们是在聊电视剧《老友记》吗
You guys talking about that show, "Friends"?
人们总说"为什么里面没有黑人老友"
People always say, "Why was there no black friend?"
因为任何一个脑子没病的黑人
Because no reasonable black man
都不会跟那帮人当朋友
would hang out with those people.
他等着说出这段话
He's been waiting to get that off his chest
大概等了20年了吧
since the mid-'90s.
你知道我刚意识到什么吗
You know what I just realized?
我还没有试过以穷人身份跟人交朋友
I've never tried to make friends as a not-rich person.
你交了我这个朋友啊
You made friends with me.
虽然我被强迫中奖 但也算数啊
Against my will, but still.
你猜我要干嘛
Guess what I'm doing?
给我上求职网站看人履历的动力吗
Motivating me to look at resumes on monster.com?
我现在要去跟人交朋友
I'm gonna make a friend right now.
我服务区有一个头发称得上干净的姑娘
There's a girl in my section with clean-ish looking hair.
说到"毛发" 上菜
Speaking of hair, pick up.
科布沙拉
Cobb salad.
麦克斯 我这个交友笑容如何
Max, how's this for my friend-making smile?
你的牙齿总数是不是比我多啊
Do you have more teeth than me?
这是您的沙拉 调味料分开放了
Here's you salad. Dressing on the side.
我自己也是"调分放"那种女孩
I'm sort of a "DOS" gal myself.
好的
Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
或许我们哪天应该一起把沙拉言欢
Maybe we should, I don't know, grab a couple salads sometime.
点评网特别说了
The Yelp review specifically said
服务员绝对不会鸟我
I would be ignored by the waitstaff.
你的沙拉里有"毛"
There's hair in your salad.
不好意思
Excuse me.
这里的水就是那个颜色
The water's supposed to be that color.
不 不是的
No, no.
我觉得你这么勇敢很酷
I just think it's cool how brave you were
敢于跟陌生人交朋友
to put yourself out there like that.
我上一次被说酷 还是拥有一张黑卡
I haven't been called cool since I had a black card
与3/4个岛的时候呢
and owned 3/4 of an island.
我叫瑞秋 这位是凯西
I'm Rachel. This is Kathy.
我叫卡洛琳
I'm Caroline,
你们绝对想不到我有多勇敢
and you have no idea how brave I am.
你们应该看看我洗澡的地方
You should see where I shower.
她应该来参加我们的派对
She should come to our party.
她刚搬来威廉斯堡
She just moved to Williamsburg,
我们明天打算举办一个派对
and we're having a party tomorrow.
-你应该一起来 -其实呢
- You should come. - Oh, you know what?
我明晚有点忙 因为我要去参加你的派对
I'm busy tomorrow night because I'm going to your party!
那些搞播客的人都没她这么渴求认同
I've seen people with podcasts less desperate for approval.
麦克斯 我昨晚玩得超开心
Max, I had the most amazing night.
我也是 贝姬刚走
Me too. Becky just left.
她明天得早起
She has to get up early tomorrow.
不是要炫耀 但她要在电视剧《警察世家》中
Not to brag, but she's playing a dead hooker
演死掉的妓女
on "Blue Bloods."
所以她来这里做调查学习吗
Oh, so she came here for research.
我的新朋友们瑞秋与凯西
Anyways, my new friends Rachel and Kathy
以及派对上的所有人都好温暖与正能量
and everybody there were so warm and positive.
跟一群发愤图强并努力向前的人相处
It was so refreshing to be around people
好让人精神振作啊
who were super driven and focused.
而且昨晚我们的聊天特别有意思
And we had such interesting conversations.
老实说 跟她们聊完天后
Honestly, after talking to them,
我觉得没有什么事是做不到的
I felt like anything is possible.
你们嗑药啦
Oh, you guys did molly?
现在我嫉妒了
Now I'm jealous.
这些人不需要靠嗑药来快乐
These people don't need drugs to be happy.
所以是邪教
Oh, so it's a cult.
你是从哪推理出他们是邪教
How did you get cult from that?
你觉得我唯一能交到朋友的方法
You think the only way I can make friends
就是加入邪教吗
is by joining a cult?
不是
No.
你也可以靠分享口香糖交友啊
You could also always have gum.
其实 他们人好到
In fact, they're so nice,
他们邀请你一起去欢度周末
they invited you to come for the weekend.
新鲜乡村空气
Fresh country air.
-恕难从命 -美丽自然风光
- No thanks. - Gorgeous views.
-欣赏无能 -免费食物酒水
- Not for me. - Free food and booze.
我不介意周末加入一下邪教
I could be in a cult for the weekend.
这里真是太棒了
This place is amazing.
对啊 高大上
I know. Fancy.
刚才那也是我第一次坐巴士
And that was the first bus I've been on
没有碰到有人用衣服盖着玩"鸟"
where I didn't see an under-the-blanket handy.
我叫"托福儿" 刚才坐同一班巴士
I'm Topher. From the bus.
你刚才一直丢葵花籽到我头发上
You were throwing sunflower seeds in my hair.
她叫果酱女郎
This is Lady Marmalade.
名字叫托福儿的人不应该有
People named Topher shouldn't be allowed
命名其他活体生物的权利
to name other living things.
请不要取笑她
Please don't make fun of her.
她有季节性抑郁症
She has seasonal depression.
我俩都有
We both do.
卡洛琳 你来真是太好了
Hey, Caroline, I'm so glad you could come.
想必你就是...
And you must be...
饿死鬼投胎
Starving.
整盘直接给我就行了
Just give me the tray.
她是麦克斯
This is Max.
谢谢你邀请我们一起来
Thank you so much for inviting us.
我们上次被人邀请 是去面试拍黄片
Yeah, the last invitation we got was to audition for porn.
也不太算是邀请
Less of an invitation;
基本上就是敞篷车里有人喊
more of a shout from a convertible.
"美女们有兴趣拍黄片吗"
"You girls want to do porn?"
伊莱恩很快就会出来
Well, Elaine will be out in a minute,
在此之前 就继续当你们棒棒哒自己吧
so in the meantime, just be your awesome self.
她是不是很赞
Isn't she great?
你看 这里很好
So see? It's nice here.
你还觉得这里是邪教呢
And you thought it was a cult.
我也曾以为餐厅里的花生没沾到蛋上呢
I also thought peanuts never touched the eggs at the diner,
结果那女士过敏翘辫子了
but then that lady died.
欢迎各位
Welcome, everyone.
你好啊 伊莱恩
Hi, Elaine.
这个屋子里只有两条规矩
There are only two rules in this house:
彼此友爱
love one another
以及不许跟邻居说话
and don't talk to the neighbors.
我恨死他们了
I hate them.
我很高兴你们大家全都能出席
I'm so glad you all could make it.
除了杰瑞不能来
Oh, except Jerry.
他去做激光矫正手术
He's getting LASIK.
他当初就该听我的 我让他多吃甘蓝菜
He should've listened. I told him to eat more kale.
甘蓝菜对眼睛好
Kale is good for the eyes.
好了
Okay.
大家把这里当自己家吧
Now make yourselves at home.
是指不付房租
You mean don't pay our rent
一听到走廊有人就躲起来吗
and hide every time we hear someone in the hall?
伊莱恩 这位是卡洛琳
Elaine, this is Caroline,
我们的新朋友
our new friend.
你好 卡洛琳
Hello, Caroline.
久仰美名
I've heard so many wonderful things.
这位是
And you are?
正在寻觅蘸酱
Looking for some dipping sauces.
我是麦克斯
I'm Max.
一位知道自己想要什么的姑娘 我喜欢
A lady who knows what she wants. I like that.
我的前夫也知道自己想要什么
My ex-husband knew what he wanted:
成为一名女性
to be a woman.
他做到了
And now he is.
我好想她
I miss her.
以及我的所有鞋子
And all my shoes.
我理解你的心情 姐们
I hear you, sister.
但说真的 有没有蜂蜜芥末酱
But seriously, something like a honey mustard
或任何法式芥末酱都行
or really anything in the Dijon world.
哇 这果子不好啃
Whoo, she's a tough nut.
我的最爱
My favorite kind.
腰果除外
Except for cashews.
麦克斯 伊莱恩赞赞哒
Max, Elaine is amazing.
环顾四周
Look around.
这就是我的新社交圈
This is my new social circle.
这是我见过最悲哀的圈了
This is the saddest circle I've seen
上一次是我妈在沃尔玛地板上尿出个圈
since my mom peed on the floor at Wal-Mart.
你就不能承认这不是邪教吗
Can you just admit it's not a cult?
大家围过来
Everyone gather 'round.
我们来进行相互眼神交流
Let's have some mutual eye contact.
这个好 正常人都该这样
That's nice. That's just being a person.
望向站在你身旁的人
Look to the person next to you,
用你的双眼 向他们打开心灵大门
and open the door to them with your eyes.
小贱人 姐的那扇门关死了
Bitch, that door is locked.
干得漂亮
Nicely done.
好了 各位
All right, everyone.
跟我一起背诵我们的真言
I'd like us to recite our mantra.
最佳自我在心中 上天保佑必不空
My best is my best, and that's why I'm blessed.
最佳自我在心中
My best is my best,
上天保佑必不空
and that's why I'm blessed.
别含糊不清 康妮
Don't mumble, Connie.
最佳自我在心中
My best is my best,
上天保佑必不空
and that's why I'm blessed.
好吧 的确是邪教
Okay, it's a cult.
有那么一点啦
Little bit.
最佳自我在心中
My best is my best...
好了 各位
All right, everyone.
让碗的声音洗涤你们
Let the sound of the bowls wash over you,
净化全身 从头到脚
cleansing you from head to toe
由外而内
and everywhere in-between.
这年头当个碗也不容易啊
These bowls got their work cut out for them.
各位 请闭上眼 放空大脑
Everyone, close your eyes and quiet the mind,
感受治愈的心灵震波
and receive the healing vibrations.
让我们沐浴在声音里吧 尤金
Sound bathe us, Eugene.
当你们感知到碗的召唤
When you feel called to join the bowls,
开始轻柔地...
begin with a soft...
我一般是从轻柔地口交开始
I usually begin with a soft hummer.
我们要怎么摆脱这个...
How are we gonna get out of this?
不如实事求是地叫它
Let's just call it what it is:
邪教
a cult.
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere
除非等我看了碗里有什么
until I see what's in those bowls.
我希望是意大利宽面
I'm hoping for fettuccini.
我希望不是意大利宽面
I hope it's not fettuccini
因为我真的不喜欢奶油为主的酱料
because I really don't like cream-based sauces.
闭嘴行吗
Do you mind?
这对果酱女郎很重要
This is important for Lady Marmalade.
她有纤维肌痛症
She has fibromyalgia.
纤维肌痛症和季节性抑郁
Fibromyalgia and seasonal depression?
你这条算是头奖级的神犬啊
You really won the dog lottery.
好了 各位
All right, everyone.
等你们准备好了 就可以
You may gently bring your energy
缓缓将你们的能量
back into the room
带回这间房间
whenever you feel ready.
我们必须离开这里
We got to get out of here.
我们该怎么办 这地方荒无人烟
What are we gonna do? We're in the middle of nowhere.
你知道啥能拯救我们于水深火热中吗
You know what would save the day right now?
奶步
Boober.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
声音洗礼时 你有感受到什么吗
Did anything come up for you during the sound bath?
感受到沙嗲鸡肉串反胃 但还好
A little bit of the chicken satay, but all good.
麦克斯 你呢
Max, how are you?
你有任何触动吗
Were you touched at all?
在高中时 我被一位天使[触]摸过
In high school, I was touched by an angel.
严格来说 他的名字叫
Well, technically, his name was...
天屎
Angel.
我知道这一切看上去就像是胡说八道
I know this probably all seems like a lot of hooey,
但我保证你们醒来会觉得神清气爽
but I assure you you'll wake up feeling refreshed.
尤金做的煎饼早餐超级好吃
And Eugene makes a hell of a pancake breakfast.
他用的是意大利乳清奶酪哦
He uses ricotta.
我们必须留下
We're staying.
乳清奶酪 汝请留下
I mean, ricotta? We gotta.
那好吧
I guess so.
就像待在提供住宿和早餐的旅馆
It'll be like staying at a B and B
老板是无说服力版的科学神教教主
run by a lame Ron Hubbard.
晚安 各位
Goodnight, everyone.
瑞秋已经把你们的房间安排好了
Rachel has your room assignments.
卡洛琳 你跟我住一间
Caroline, you're sharing a room with me.
好棒
Yay.
麦克斯 你跟托福儿和果酱女郎住一间
Max, you're sharing a room with Topher and Lady Marmalade.
为啥我从来都捞不着好室友
Can I ever get a good roommate?
别害怕
And do not fear.
黎明破晓前 你们每个人都有机会
Before the night is over, each of you will have a chance
跟我做爱
to make love with me.
其余的鸡肉串也反上来了
And the rest of the satay just came up.
日出之前 我们的月亮将会合一
Before the sunrise, our moons will unite.
我猜她的"月亮"肯定没除毛
Well, I'm guessing her moon's not waxed.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
卡洛琳 你在哪里
Caroline, where are you?
卡洛琳
Caroline?
我还以为你是伊莱恩
I thought you were gonna be Elaine...
我还不够醉 "干"不下去啊
and I'm not drunk enough for that!
对了 你的粉红猪把鼻头拱出来了
By the way, the piglet's popping the snout out.
我还以为你是伊莱恩
Oh, I thought you were gonna be Elaine.
我还以为我14岁时会死掉呢
And I thought I was gonna be dead at 14,
但你总不可能事事顺心吧
but you can't always get what you want.
麦克斯
Max!
麦克斯 天啊 你没事吧
Max, oh, my God. Are you okay?
拜托告诉我 伊莱恩没有对你下手
Please tell me Elaine didn't get to you.
否则我会没脸活下去
I could never live with myself.
或跟你住下去
Or you.
抱歉我这么久才到达高潮
I'm sorry it took me so long to climax.
我知道我在高潮门前好一阵子才成功进去
I know I was almost there for quite some time.
麦克斯 卡洛琳 你们俩在外面干嘛
Max, Caroline, what are you doing out here?
我们迫切地等待
We were just anxiously awaiting
您的临幸
intercourse with you.
真的吗
Really?
因为除非那袋子装的全是情趣用具
'Cause unless that bag's full of marital aids,
否则你们看起来是想溜走
it looks like you're trying to sneak out.
听着 伊莱恩
Look, Elaine,
这一切我很难接受 无意冒犯
this is all a lot, and no offense,
但我今年的第一炮
but you can't be the first person
对象不能是你
I have sex with this year.
我明白你们俩都觉得有点不知所措
I understand that you're both feeling a little overwhelmed,
但在你们走之前 我们何不以集体的形式
but before you go, why don't we discuss this as a group
疗愈般地讨论一下
in a healing way?
好的 尤金 待着别动
All right, Eugene, stay where you are.
你需要休息
You need some rest.
或许需要补充蛋白质
Maybe a little protein.
不如我们直接走吧
So you know what? We're just gonna go.
你可以跟门口那人说
You can tell that guy at the door
让他让开 好让我们...
he can just step aside so we can,
你懂的 飞奔离开
you know, start running.
卡洛琳 你们随时都可以走
Caroline, you are free to go at any time.
那我们可以现在走吗
So we can go right now?
不行
No.
卡洛琳 你何不坐这边 瑞秋
Caroline, why don't you sit here, and Rachel,
把麦克斯带到锣那边
bring Max over by the gong.
Siri 记得提醒我申请锣烟枪[音似]的专利
Siri, remind me to patent a gong bong.
顺便提醒我弄个有Siri的手机
Also remind me to get a phone with Siri.
我知道今晚还有人没能跟我上床
Now, I know some of you have not yet laid with me tonight...
但我注意到
But it's come to my attention
我们中间有一位NN
that we have an N.N. in our midst.
-什么 -是谁
- What? - Who?
问一下 什么是NN
Quick Q on the N.N.
这个N是代表玉米脆片的意思吗
Do either of those Ns stand for nachos?
NN代表的是"消极的奈利"
N.N. stands for Negative Nelly.
"消极的南希"已经被另一个抢注了
Negative Nancy was already trademarked
而那个团体的领导是我的前夫 南希
by another group run by my ex-husband, Nancy.
卡洛琳 你知道这个NN可能会是谁人吗
Caroline, do you have any idea who this N.N. could be?
你是要问"谁"吗 我不知道
I believe it's "whom" And no, I don't.
卡洛琳 你现在过着你想要的人生吗
Caroline, are you where you want to be in life?
差了十万八千里
Oh, God, no.
你会觉得是因为某人在扯你后腿吗
And would you say there's someone holding you back?
我的确是觉得
Well, I do feel like
每天听女演员艾米·舒默的事
hearing about Amy Schumer every day
有点让我感到无力
makes me feel a little "less than."
卡洛琳 在这间屋子里的某人
Caroline, is there someone in this room
就是你带来的那位棕发人士
who you brought with brown hair
她的消极奈利气息
whose Negative Nelly-ness
是不是阻挡了你的前路而你不自知呢
is blocking you in ways you don't even realize?
等等
Wait a minute.
我怎么开始感觉到是在说我
I'm starting to think this is about me.
经过短短几小时与麦克斯的相处
Just having spent a few short hours with Max
并录下了你们所有的对话
and recording all your conversations...
很显然
It's pretty clear
她在你的成功道路上
that she is undermining your path to success
用她的俏皮话与双关语在搞破坏
with her wisecracks and wordplay.
听我说
Look.
麦克斯看起来可能很消极 她也的确是
Max might seem negative, because she is,
但如果你的人生像她一般 你也会消极
but you would be, too, if you were her.
她这一生被人忽视 拒之门外
She's been neglected, rejected,
被人击倒 吐口水
knocked down, and spat on.
其中某些是相互的
Some of that was consensual.
你看 这就很正面积极啊
See? That was positive.
所以你愿意放弃这一切潜在人脉
So you will give up all these potential connections
就为了她一人吗
just for her?
卡洛琳 我曾经住在泽西城
Caroline, I used to live in Jersey City,
而我现在搬到新泽西更好的地区了呢
and now I live in a better part of New Jersey.
伊莱恩 我本以为我需要交些新朋友
Elaine, I thought I needed to make new friends,
所以我才沦落到这里
and that's how I wound up here,
但原来 我只需要麦克斯一人
but turns out all I needed was Max.
我愿意在她身上赌一把
I'll take my chances with her.
天大的错误啊
Huge mistake.
天大
Huge.
那两位走吧
Well, then you're free to go.
把账结了就行了
Just need to settle up your bill.
这周末派对只对朋友免费
This weekend is only free for friends.
瑞秋
Rachel.
我吃了一只价值700块的虾吗
I ate $700 worth of shrimp?
感觉的确是差不多这个数
That seems about right.
我们不能付这个钱
We can't pay that.
有船需要我们清理
Is there a ship we can scrub?
还是同志名人需要形婚的吗
Or a gay celebrity we can marry?
别担心 我来跟伊莱恩处理
Don't worry. I'll settle up with Elaine.
你收上天恩赐的信用卡吗
Do you accept nature's credit card?
滚出去
Get out.
真不敢相信我唯一能交到朋友的方法
I can't believe the only way I can make a friend
是加入邪教
is to join a cult.
你跟我交了朋友啊 我不是邪教中人
Well, you made friends with me, and I'm not in a cult...
已金盆洗手
anymore.
麦克斯 有一天我们也能像你跟贝姬那样吗
Max, are you and I gonna be like you and Becky someday?
除非我们其中一人能变得超级超级
Not unless one of us gets really, really,
是变得比现在酷炫超级多才行
I mean, so much cooler.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
我会不会就只是你的某个服务员同事
Am I gonna be just some waitress you used to know?
这样我会心碎的
'Cause that would kill me.
我从来不这样想你
I don't think of you that way at all.
我是指 你不够格当服务员
I mean as a waitress.
的确 我跟贝姬曾经是同事
Look, yes, Becky and I worked together,
也的确 我们也曾一起有过一个创业梦想
and yes, we had kind of a business dream, too,
但你和我所拥有的远远不止如此
but you and I have so much more than that.
你跟我马上就要死在森林里了
You and I are about to die in the woods.
你看
Look.
我们绝对要上这台车
We are getting in that car
哪怕车主其中一只手是钩子
even if this guy has a hook for a hand.
还好咩
Wazzup?
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我从没想过大晚上在阴暗的马路上
I never thought I'd be happy to see Oleg
见到奥列格会这么开心
on a dark road at night.
苏菲 你们俩在这里干嘛呢
Sophie, what are you guys doing here?
麦克斯把所在位置发给我了
Oh, well, Max texted me her location.
说如果她没有回复消息
Said if I didn't hear back from her,
就表示你们被邪教挟持 得来救你们
you'd been abducted by the cult and to come rescue you.
我也曾入过魔教
I was in a cult once.
入过"雅芳"的魔
It's called Avon.
所以你早早就确定我交不到普通朋友
So you were so certain I couldn't make a normal friend
所以先安排好逃生计划吗
you had an escape plan?
有时候我"消极有好报"啊
Hey, sometimes my negativity pays off.
而有时候则会害我被关进百货拘留所
Sometimes it gets me in mall jail.